AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records 5478
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VIIIb: System Federations and Matters Pertaining to Individual System Federations, 1917-1961
  - Colorado and Southern Railway, 1940-1965 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    Code No. 22-140, pt. 2; Mar. 4, 1940 - Dec. 29, 1965; See also box 21
  - Cincinnati Union Terminal Railroad, 1949-1962 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    Code No. 22-150, pt. 3; Dec. 27, 1949 - May 14, 1962; See also box 21
  - Texas and New Orleans Railroad, 1941-1963 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    Code No. 22-162, pt. 1; Mar. 13, 1941 - Dec. 23, 1963; See also box 21
- Series XXVIIb: Executive Council - Minutes and Correspondence, 1921-1961
  - Executive Council Meetings, 1957-1966 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    Code No. 24-18, pt. 7; Jan. 11, 1957 - May 31, 1966; See also box 23
  - Railway Labor Executives Assoc. - meetings, minutes and correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    Code No. 24-19, pt. 7; Jan. 6, 1950 - Oct. 26, 1955; See also box 23
  - Railway Labor Executives Assoc. - meetings, minutes and correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    Code No. 24-19, pt. 10; Apr. 3, 1961 - Aug. 14, 1963; See also box 23
  - Railway Labor Executives Assoc. - meetings, minutes and correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    Code No. 24-19, pt. 11; Sept. 4, 1963 - Mar. 26, 1965; See also box 23
  - Railway Labor Executives Assoc. - meetings, minutes and correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    Code No. 24-19, pt. 12; Apr. 28, 1965 - Jun. 1, 1966; See also box 23
  - Railway Labor Executives Assoc. - meetings, minutes and correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    Code No. 24-19, pt. 13; Jun. 23, 1966 - Dec. 18, 1967; See also box 23
  - Railway Labor Executives Assoc. - meetings, minutes and correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    Code No. 24-19, pt. 14; Nov. 15, 1967 - Dec. 26, 1968; See also box 23
  - Index to Minutes of Meetings, 1942-1943 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    Code No. 24-19-A, pt. 10; Jan. 7-9, 1942 - Dec. 8, 1943; See also box 24
  - Index to Minutes of Meetings, 1944-1946 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    Code No. 24-19-A, pt. 11; Feb. 23, 1944 - Dec. 4-5, 1946; See also box 24
  - Index to Minutes of Meetings, 1947-1949 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    Code No. 24-19-A, pt. 12; Feb. 26, 1947 - Sept. 28-30, 1949; See also box 24
  - Index to Minutes of Meetings, 1950-1953 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    Code No. 24-19-A, pt. 13; Jan. 18-20, 1950 - Mar. 26-27, 1953; See also box 24
  - Index to Minutes of Meetings, 1953-1956 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    Code No. 24-19-A, pt. 14; Apr. 28-30, 1953 - Nov. 27, 1956; See also box 24
  - Index to Minutes of Meetings, 1957-1958 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    Code No. 24-19-A, pt. 15; Jan. 8, 1957 - Dec. 10, 1958; See also box 24
  - Index to Minutes of Meetings, 1959-1961 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    Code No. 24-19-A, pt. 16; Jan. 14, 1959 - Jun. 7, 1961; See also box 24
  - Index to Minutes of Meetings, 1961-1963 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    Code No. 24-19-A, pt. 17; Jul. 17, 1961 - May 1, 1963; See also box 24
  - Index to Minutes of Meetings, 1963-1964 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    Code No. 24-19-A, pt. 18; Jun. 26, 1963 - Nov. 9, 1964; See also box 24
  - Index to Minutes of Meetings, 1965 (Box 166, Folder 6)
    Code No. 24-19-A, pt. 19; Jan. 1965 - Nov. 30, 1965; See also box 24
  - Index to Minutes of Meetings, 1966 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    Code No. 24-19-A, pt. 20; Jan. 18, 1966 - Dec. 6, 1966; See also box 24
  - Index to Minutes of Meetings, 1967 (Box 167, Folder 2)
    Code No. 24-19-A, pt. 21; Jan. 11, 1967 - Nov. 29, 1967; See also box 24
  - Index to Minutes of Meetings, 1968 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    Code No. 24-19-A, pt. 22; Jan. 8, 1968 - Dec. 3, 1968; See also box 24
  - Index to Minutes of Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    Code No. 24-19-A, pt. 23; Jan. 25, 1969 - Dec. 8, 1970; See also box 24
  - Railway Labor Executives Association - Financial Reports, 1956 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    Code No. 24-19-B, pt. 1; Jun. 1, 1956 - Dec. 1956
  - Railway Labor Executive Association - Financial Reports, 1957-1966 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    Code No. 24-19-B, pt. 2; Jan. 1957 - Apr. 1966
  - Index to Minutes of Meetings, 1929-1949 (Box 167, Folder 7)
    Code No. 24-19-C, Index; Jan. 30-31, 1929 - Sept. 28-30, 1949; See also box 24
  - Clippings only - re: railroad wages, 1932 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    Code No. 24-19-D; See also box 24
  - Labor Policy - Labor Cooperative Education and Publishing Society to inc. Annual Report, 1942-1950 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    Code No. 26-19, pt. 4; See also box 24
  - Labor Policy - Labor Cooperative Education and Publishing Society to inc. Annual Report, 1950-1957 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    Code No. 26-19, pt. 5; See also box 24
  - Labor Policy - Labor Cooperative Education and Publishing Society to inc. Annual Report, 1957-1959 (Box 168, Folder 4)
    Code no. 26-19, pt. 6; See also box 24
  - Labor Policy - Labor Cooperative Education and Publishing Society to inc. Annual Report, 1960-1962 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    Code No. 26-19, pt. 7; See also box 24
  - Labor Policy - Labor Cooperative Education and Publishing Society to inc. Annual Report, 1962-1965 (Box 168, Folder 6)
    Code No. 26-19, pt. 8; See also box 24
  - Labor Cooperative Educational and Publishing Society - Monthly Report, 1944-1948 (Box 168, Folder 7)
    Code No. 26-19-A, pt. 4; See also box 24
  - Labor Cooperative Educational and Publishing Society - Monthly Report, 1949-1960 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    Code No. 26-19-A, pt. 5; See also box 24
  - Financial Minutes of Labor Cooperative Educational Publishing Society, 1949-1960 (Box 169, Folder 2)
    Code No. 26-19-A, pt. 6; See also box 24
- Series XXV: Railroad Employees' Department-Master File of Official Circulars, 1916-1867
  Official and department circulars of the Railway Employees' Department, 1916-1967, on issues affecting the individual unions affiliated with the Railway Employee' Department. Major issues highlighted throughout the circulars include: the move to abolish p
  - Railroad Employees' Department-Master File of Official Circulars, 1916-1918 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    pt. 1, no. 27-86
  - Railroad Employees' Department-Master File of Official Circulars, 1919-1920 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    pt. 2, no 87-127
  - Railroad Employees' Department-Master File of Official Circulars, 1921 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    pt. 3, 128-134
  - Railroad Employees' Department-Master File of Official Circulars, 1922-1923 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    pt. 4
  - Railroad Employees' Department-Master File of Official Circulars, 1924-1931 (Box 169, Folder 7)
    pt. 5
  - Department Circulars, 1950-1954 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    Code No. 1821-2010-21; Oct. 12, 1950 - Aug. 30, 1954
  - Department Circulars, 1954-1956 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    Code No. 2010-22-2357-10; Sept. 3, 1954 - Dec. 13, 1956
  - Department Circulars, 1957-1959 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    Code No. 2361-2399; Mar. 5, 1957 - Mar. 20, 1959
  - Department Circulars, 1959-1960 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    Code No. 2400-2357-30; May 22, 1959 - Nov. 17, 1960
  - Department Circulars, 1961-1962 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    Code No. 2431-2459; Jan. 20, 1961 - Jul. 9, 1962
  - Department Circulars, 1964-1966 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    Code No. 29-854, pt. 19; Sept. 1, 1964 - Sept. 14, 1966; See also box 28
  - Miscellaneous circulars and organizing material (Box 176, Folder 1)
    40 hour committee, organizing flyers, negotiating flyers and supervisors agreements
  - Miscellaneous files on National Agreement - correspondence and minutes, 1918-1922 (Box 177, Folder 1)